symbolab.com 2018-12-18

# EqsQuest Privacy Policy

EqsQuest Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally
identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security,
is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single
person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear
understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in
accordance with our Website (as such term is defined in our Terms and Conditions of Use).
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit Website?
When ordering or registering on our Website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email
address or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our Website or enter information on our Website.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our
newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the Website, or use certain other Website
features in the following ways:
     •   To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings
         in which you are most interested.
     •   To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
How do we protect visitor information?
Our Website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your
visit to our Website as safe as possible.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number
of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information
confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer
(SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to
maintain the safety of your personal information.
All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
Children
The Website and any of its services is not directed to children under the age of 13 (in some countries, stricter
age limits may apply. See our Terms and Conditions of Use.) We do not knowingly collect personal
information from children under 13 or under the applicable age limit. If you are under the Age Limit, do not
use the Service and do not provide any personal information to us. If you are a parent of a child under the
Age Limit and become aware that your child has provided personal information to the Website, please

                                                       -2-
contact us at and you may request exercise of your applicable access, rectification, cancellation, and/or
objection rights.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through
your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your
browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember
and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based
on previous or current Website activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also
use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about Website traffic and Website interaction so that we can
offer better Website experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
    • Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
    • Compile aggregate data about Website traffic and Website interactions in order to offer better
         Website experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track
         this information on our behalf.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn
off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little
different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If users disable cookies in their browser:
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It will turn off some of the features that make your
Website experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
However, you can still place orders
registration, practice, notes
.
Third Party Disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless
we provide you with advance notice. This does not include Website hosting partners and other parties who
assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree
to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is
appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Website policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property,
or                                                                                                        safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing,
advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
We do not include or offer third party products or services on our Website.
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in
place            to         provide           a          positive          experience         for          users.
https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

                                                        -3-
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our Website.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Website. Google's use of the DART cookie
enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Website and other sites on the Internet. Users
may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
     • Google Display Network Impression Reporting
     • Demographics and Interests Reporting
     • DoubleClick Platform Integration
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics
cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to
compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to
our Website.
Opting out:
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page.
Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently
using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a
privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the
United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable
information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly
the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this
policy.      -      See      more       at:     http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-
caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
Users can visit our Website anonymously
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first
significant page after entering our Website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:
     • On our Privacy Policy Page
Users are able to change their personal information:
     • By emailing us
How does our Website handle do not track signals?
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track
(DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our Website allow third party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online
Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's
consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and
online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

                                                     -4-
We do not specifically market to children under 13.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the
concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the
globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is
critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action,
should a data breach occur:
We will notify the users via email
     • Within 7 business days
We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue
legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle
requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have
recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data
processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for
commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells
out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
     • Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
     • Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders
     • We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
              o Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original
                 transaction has occurred
To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
     • NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
     • Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
     • Include the physical address of our business or Website headquarters
     • Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
     • Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
     • Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at
     • Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.
     • and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the
information below.
Eqsquest
PO Box 39305

                          -5-
Tel Aviv
Merkaz
6139201
Israel
support@eqsquest.com
Last Edited on 2017-01-15
